{
    "subject": "resource/Dr\u00f8bak",
    "predicate": "ontology/leaderName",
    "object": "resource/Joseph_Stalin",
    "human_readable": "The leader name of Dr\u00f8bak is Joseph Stalin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9858152866363525,
            "question": "Is Joseph Stalin the leader of Dr\u00f8bak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9857025742530823,
            "question": "Does Dr\u00f8bak have a leader named Joseph Stalin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9237437844276428,
            "question": "What is the name of the leader in Dr\u00f8bak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9140223264694214,
            "question": "Is Joseph Stalin associated with Dr\u00f8bak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8714481592178345,
            "question": "Who is the leader of Dr\u00f8bak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8288837671279907,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Joseph Stalin is the leader?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7465764284133911,
            "question": "Who holds the position of leader in Dr\u00f8bak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7246509194374084,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the leader of Dr\u00f8bak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6187776923179626,
            "question": "What is Joseph Stalin known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5831980109214783,
            "question": "Where does Joseph Stalin lead?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The leader name of Dr\u00f8bak is Joseph Stalin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5758_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Joseph Stalin known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5758_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the leader of Dr\u00f8bak?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5758_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who holds the position of leader in Dr\u00f8bak?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5758_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5758_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5758_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5758_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5758_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5758_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5758_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5758_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5758_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5758_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5758_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text mentions Glenn Christiansen as the leader of Dr\u00f8bak Frogn Idrettslag, not Joseph Stalin.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nThe context information contains a mention of \"the leader Glenn Christiansen\" and later mentions of Stalin, but it clearly states that the leader of Dr\u00f8bak Frogn Idrettslag is Glenn Christiansen, not Joseph Stalin."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The information provided does not mention any leader named Joseph Stalin for the town of Dr\u00f8bak. Joseph Stalin was a Soviet politician and the leader mentioned in the first document pertains to his role during World War II, specifically regarding Poland and Norway, not as a leader of Dr\u00f8bak."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}